Markierra Dixon

(832) 396-4254 | Markierradixon@gmail.com | Houston, TX https://www.linkedin.com/in/markierra-dixon | https://github.com/Markierra

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A Web developer with over 350+ hours of training and experience. I'm an attentive problem solver with an interest in attaining a career path that will allow me the opportunity to excel and highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- Visual Studio Code

- Git
- Github
- Unit Testing with Mocha & Jest
- Bootstrap
- **SCRUM**

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Web Developer Program | February 2023 - Current

Training Participant (in progress)

- Participating in an 22 week, 460+ hour Junior Web Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning fundamentals of JavaScript, programming fundamentals, developer tools, git and problem solving

Necco | Lexington, KY | July 2022 - January 2023 Independent Living Life Coach

- Served as a liaison between Necco, placement agencies and all other necessary community resource entities
- Assisted young adults through intake by ensuring completion of all initial documentation within allotted time frame and ensured their placement was conducive to their needs
- Provided ongoing training and support to young adults as it relates to their independence and utilized resources to solve issues they may have
- Created various monthly reports and appropriately completed medicaid documentation
- Participated in service meetings which may include community support representatives, state worker, outpatient clinician, school system, and other invested parties

Fayette Regional Juvenile Detention Center| Lexington, KY | January 2022 - April 2022

Youth Worker I

- Maintained custody of juveniles in a custodial security setting and monitored activities
- Assisted juveniles in interpersonal skill development
- Maintained shift logs on juvenile's activities and completed incident reports as needed
- Performed counts and/or wellness checks for juveniles

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Criminal Justice | August 2018 - May 2019

Eastern Kentucky University: College of Justice, Safety & Military Science